<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<emails>
  <email>
    <subject> Parent Invitation </subject>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[  
<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
    <head>
        <meta charset="utf-8">
        <style type="text/css">
        	body{
        		font-family: arial;
        		font-size: 18px;
        		color: #333;
        	}
			.pdf{
				width: 1236px;
				margin: 0 auto;
				padding: 40px 50px;
				box-sizing: border-box;
				-webkit-box-sizing: border-box;
			}
			.logo{
				width: 750px;
				margin: 0 auto;
				text-align: center;
				margin-bottom: 50px;
        margin-top:100px;
			}
			.logo img{
				width: 100%;
			}
			.itc{
				font-weight: 700;
				font-style: italic;
				font-size: 20px;
			}
			h3{
				font-size: 36px;
				font-style: italic;
				margin: 30px 0 20px 0;
			}
			.left,.right{
				width: 49%;
				display: inline-block;
				vertical-align: top;
			}
			.left{
				padding-right: 20px;
				box-sizing: border-box;
				-webkit-box-sizing: border-box;
			}
			button{
				padding: 10px 15px;
				border-radius: 15px;
				border: 0;
				color: #fff;
				font-size: 16px;
				outline: none;
				cursor: pointer;
			}
			.left button{
				background: #41B23B;
			}
			.right button{
				background: #D11F27;
			}
			a{
				color: #30579F;
			}
			.footer{
				border-top: 2px solid #ccc;
				margin-top: 40px;
				text-align: right;
				padding-top: 5px;
				font-size: 13px;
			}
			.footer div{
				display: inline-block;
				vertical-align: center;
			}
			.footer p{
				margin: 0;
				line-height: 20px;
			}
			.footer p:first-child{
				font-weight: 700;
				font-size: 19px;
			}
			.footer img{
				width: 35px;
			}
        </style>
    </head>
    <body style="font-family: arial;font-size: 20px;color: #333;width: 1200px;">
		
			<div class="pdf">
			<div class="logo">
				<img src="[staticdomain]/Content/images/logo2.png">
			</div>
			<div class="arial">
				<p>Throughout the school year, students in your child’s prekindergarten classroom are being given special activities to help their teacher track their progress. The teacher looks at the results of this “progress monitoring” to determine if the children are developing the skills they will need for kindergarten and their later school years.</p>
				<p>The CIRCLE Progress Monitoring tool helps your child’s teacher identify learning areas in which your child is developing a level of understanding that is expected for his or her age. The tool also identifies areas in which your child might need more targeted support and practice.</p>
				<p>If your child is meeting or exceeding the expectation for his or her age, the teacher will offer additional supports to help your child progress further. If your child needs targeted support for a particular skill, then the teacher might use a variety of different teaching strategies to support that area of development.</p>
			</div>
			<div class="itc">
				<p>Your child’s scores, as well as descriptions of the areas assessed, can be found on the following page.</p>
			</div>
			<h3>What do the colors mean?</h3>
			<div class="left">
				<button>ON TRACK</button>
				<p>Your child’s score is “on track,” or within the expected range for this activity. Continue to support her/him at home with our recommended activities in this skill area listed under “what I can do at home”.</p>
			</div>
			<div class="right">
				<button>NEEDS SUPPORT</button>
				<p>Your child scored below the expected range for this activity and needs additional support. This could be for many reasons. Help support your child’s growth in this area by using our recommended activities listed under “what I can do at home”.</p>
			</div>
			<p style="margin-top:5px;">Note: The tool efficiently and reliably provides a snapshot of how your child’s learning is progressing over time. The results are NOT comprehensive, developmental assessments. The results are also NOT intended to diagnose children that may have difficulty learning or experiencing other delays. Please talk to your child’s teacher or an administrator at your child’s school if you are concerned about your child’s progress or development.</p>
			<h3>What can I do at home?</h3>
			<p style="margin-top:5px;">We provide resources to help you support your child’s development. Visit the <a href="javascript:;">CLI Engage Parent Page</a> (cliengage.org/ parents) to find easy, fun activities that target important school readiness skills.</p>
			<h3>Questions or concerns?</h3>
			<p style="margin-top:5px;margin-bottom:60px;">Your child’s teacher should be able to help answer questions about your child’s progress monitoring scores and how you can work together to build your child’s skills. Questions about the CIRCLE Progress Monitoring System or CIRCLE Activity Collection can be directed to cliengage@uth.tmc.edu.</p>
			<div class="footer">
				<div class="text">
					<p>CIRCLE Progress Monitoring is a part of the Children’s Learning Institute</p>
					<p>Learn more at childrenslearninginstitute.org</p>
				</div>
				<img src="[staticdomain]/Content/images/ParentReport_Foot_Logo.png">
			</div>
		</div>

    </body>
</html>
  ]]>
    </content>
  </email>
</emails>