<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<emails>
  <email>
    <subject>You’re Invited to Explore CLI Engage</subject>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[       
    <table  width="100%" height="100%" align="center" style="border-collapse: collapse" border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
            <tbody>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <table width="506"  height="100" style="border-collapse: collapse; margin: 0 auto;" border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
                            <tbody>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="text-align: center;"><img src="{StaticDomain}/Content/images/cli_logo.png" width="250" height="100" alt="cli_logo" /></td>
                                </tr>
                            </tbody>
                        </table>
                        <table width="506" cellpadding="0" style="border:3px solid #eee; background-color: #f8f8f8; margin: 0 auto;  text-align: left; border-radius:12px;">
                            <tbody>
                                <tr>
                                    <td height="15" width="20" style="border-top: none; border-bottom: none; border-left: none; border-right: none;">
                                    </td>
                                    <td height="15" width="460" style="border-top: none; border-bottom: none; border-left: none; border-right: none;">
                                    </td>
                                    <td height="15" width="20" style="border-top: none; border-bottom: none; border-left: none; border-right: none;">
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td width="20" style="border-top: none; border-bottom: none; border-left: none; border-right: none;"></td>
                                    <td width="460" valign="top" style="font-size: 83%; border-top: none; border-bottom: none; border-left: none; border-right: none; font-size: 13px; font-family: arial, sans-serif; color: #222222; line-height: 18px">
                                        <p style="font-weight:bold; color:#008000;">Dear {ApplicantFirstName} {ApplicantLastName},</p>
                                        <p>
                                            A child care director in your community, recently began the registration process for CLI Engage, a new professional development system being offered to Texas early childhood providers and teachers by the Texas Workforce Commission.  You’re invited to learn more the system and how you can make these resources available to all early childhood providers, teachers, and directors in your community!
                                        </p>
                                        <p>
                                            <strong>CLI Engage</strong> provides early childhood providers and teachers with free access to professional development and child progress monitoring tools through an integrated web-based platform.  The system includes <strong>eCIRCLE online professional development coursework</strong> and <strong>C-PALLS+</strong>, a validated online child progress monitoring system which measures outcomes in language and literacy, math, social and emotional development, and science concepts.  The integration of these tools will increase the use of specific instructional practices that are known to improve student development.  CLI Engage is a collaborative effort between the Texas Education Agency, Texas Workforce Commission, and the Children’s Learning Institute at UTHealth to provide these tools free of charge to early childhood providers and teachers in Texas.
                                        </p>
                                        <p>
                                            Participation in CLI Engage will allow you to:
                                            <ul>
                                                <li>Offer teachers more than 100 hours of research-based professional development coursework, including videos of best practices and hundreds of targeted classroom activities in multiple domains</li>
                                                <li>Provide access to C-PALLS+ child progress monitoring and targeted activities to meet the instructional needs of individual students</li>
                                                <li>View reports of provider/teacher professional development usage</li>
                                                <li>See child progress monitoring results for children in your community</li>
                                            </ul>
                                        </p>
                                        <p style="color:#333;">
                                            To learn more about CLI Engage, visit <a style="text-decoration: underline; cursor:pointer; color: #008000;">{CliEngageUrl}</a>.  You can explore the features of the system, including eCIRCLE professional development, C-PALLS+ child progress monitoring, and online CIRCLE activities, at <a style="text-decoration: underline; cursor:pointer; color: #008000;">{CliEngageUrl}</a>                   
                                        </p>
                                        <p style="color:#333;">
                                            Questions about the system? Contact us at <a style="text-decoration: underline; cursor:pointer; color: #008000;">cliengage@uth.tmc.edu</a>
                                        </p>
                                    </td>
                                    <td width="20" style="border-top: none; border-bottom: none; border-left: none; border-right: none;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td height="15" width="20" style="border-top: none; border-bottom: none; border-left: none; border-right: none;">
                                    </td>
                                    <td height="15" width="460" style="border-top: none; border-bottom: none; border-left: none; border-right: none;">
                                    </td>
                                    <td height="15" width="20" style="border-top: none; border-bottom: none; border-left: none; border-right: none;">
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                            </tbody>
                        </table>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
        ]]>
    </content>
  </email>
</emails>
